<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ScanGapo</string>

    <!--    MAIN FORM    -->
    <string name="scangapo">ScanGapo</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>


    <!--    REGISTER FORM  -->
    <string name="create_acc">Create Account</string>
    <string name="email_regis">Email</string>
    <string name="password_regis">Password</string>
    <string name="login_regis">Sign in</string>
    <string name="signup">Sign up</string>
    <string name="user">User</string>
    <string name="driver">Driver</string>
    <string name="employee">Employee</string>

    <!--    TRAVEL HISTORY FORM-->
    <string name="travel_history">TRAVEL HISTORY</string>

    <!--    LOCATION FORM-->
    <string name="set_location">SET A LOCATION</string>

    <!--    PROFILE FORM -->
    <string name="account">Account</string>
    <string name="profile"><u>Profile</u></string>
    <string name="accountprofile"><u>Account</u></string>
    <string name="profilee">Profile</string>
    <string name="lastname">Lastname</string>
    <string name="age">Age</string>
    <string name="middlename">Middlename</string>
    <string name="firstname">Firstname</string>
    <string name="house_lot_building">House/Lot/Building#</string>
    <string name="barangay">Barangay</string>
    <string name="city">City</string>
    <string name="update">Update</string>


    <string name="open_drawer">open</string>
    <string name="close_drawer">close</string>


    <string name="title_activity_history">History</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Travel</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Establishment</string>


    <!--    USER TYPE INFO-->

    <string name="indiv_info">Individual\nThis type of user is for people who commutes a lot and goes to a establishments</string>
    <string name="driver_info">Driver\nThis type of user is for people who works on a transportation vehicle</string>
    <string name="estab_info">Individual\nThis type of user is for people who owns an establishment</string>


    <!--    ABOUT CONTENTS-->

    <string name = "string_indiv_hometitle">Set Destination</string>
    <string name = "string_driver_hometitle">Set Vehicle</string>
    <string name = "string_est_hometitle">Employee List</string>

    <string name="string_est_overview">
        - This user can add employees to scan the customer QR Code when entering in the establishment.
    </string>

    <string name="string_est_home">
        - You can see the list of the Employees who are currently active.\n
        - You can add an employee by clicking ADD EMPLOYEE button.\n
        - You can even deactivate/activate an account by clicking the DEACTIVATE/ ACTIVATE EMPLOYEE there you can select if you want to deactivate/activate an employee\n
        - You can activate the employee scanner and QR Code by clicking their name on the list.\n
        - When the account of employee is activated for scanning, they can scan the customer QR Code, they can even generate a QR Code for the customers to scan by simply setting their Information Details on the Kebab Menu.\n
    </string>

    <string name="string_est_prof">
        - You can edit your Establishment Details.\n
        - You can change your account password by clicking the ACCOUNT tab.
    </string>

    <string name="string_est_history">
        - You can see the list of the customers that have been scanned by your employee.\n
        - You can see the list of the total numbers of your employees have scanned by clicking the COUNTS tab.
    </string>


    <string name="string_driver_overview">
        - This user can scan the generated QR Codes of the passengers and can even set the vehicle of what they want to use.
    </string>

    <string name="string_driver_home">
        - You can add a vehicle by clicking the add vehicle and input the details.\n
        - You can select the vehicle that you have registered on the plate number and it will display the details.\n
        - After you have set the vehicle that you have choose, you can now scan the QR Codes of the passengers.\n
    </string>

    <string name="string_driver_prof">
        - You can edit your Information Details that will generate as a QR Code.\n
        - You can change your account password by clicking the ACCOUNT tab.\n
    </string>

    <string name="string_driver_history">
        - You can see the list of the passengers that you have scanned on the vehicle that you have choose.\n
    </string>


    <string name="string_indiv_overview">
        - This user can generate their own QR Code for traveling and entering establishment.
    </string>

    <string name="string_indiv_home">
        - It can generate a QR Code by setting your destination and you can even add a companion.
    </string>

    <string name="string_indiv_estab">
        - It can Generate a QR Code and can add a companion for the employees to scan before you enter.\n
        - You can even scan the QR Code of the establishments using the scan button before you enter if want to.\n
    </string>

    <string name="string_indiv_prof">
        - You can edit your Information Details that will generate as a QR Code.
        - You can change your account password by clicking the ACCOUNT tab.
    </string>

    <string name="string_indiv_history">
        - You can check the list of your destination in travel history.\n
        - You can check your visited establishment by clicking the ESTABLISHMENT tab.
    </string>


</resources>